[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":45450,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":99442,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7792,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":107235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":9498,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":116734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1850,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":118585,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3343,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":121928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":7830,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":129759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your r esult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7931,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":137690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1169,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":138859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":142574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2  because  1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1130,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":143704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2484,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":146188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1081,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":147270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the f irst num ber, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":149668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1003,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":150672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":153559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1145,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":154704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2033,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":156738,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":987,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":157726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2291,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":160018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":975,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":160994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you su btract 6  to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1882,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":162877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":905,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":163782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":19325,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":183108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":40302,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":223410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6517,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":229929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1537,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":231466,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["4","5"],"rt":5553,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":237020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1137,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":238158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the in verse of  3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2296,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":240454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":948,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":241402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2712,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":244114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2227,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":246341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":7898,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":254240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5007,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":259248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":34262,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":293512,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><b r /> How ever, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":62822,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":356334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5725,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":362060,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":4256,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":366316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10- 0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":368859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":7069,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":375929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub >6</sub> ? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":378961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1133,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":380095,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2686,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":382782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1006,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":383788,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as  possible .","rt":40019,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":423807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5492,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":429300,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1121,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":430421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3255,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":433677,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3016,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":436694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4161,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":440855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3510,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":444365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2724,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":447090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4215,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":451305,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"12, 8+4=12-9=3","response_history":["12, 8+4=12-9-","12, 8+4=12-9=3"],"rt":36737,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":488043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0, because you subtract anything 9 or over. 9-9=0","response_history":["0, becaue 8","0, becau e 9-9 ","0, becaue 9-9","0, becaue 9-","0, becaue 9","0, becaue ","0, becaue","0, because yu","0, because you subtract anything 9 or over. 9-9=0"],"rt":43997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":532040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":7630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":539670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":6891,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":546562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":8645,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":555208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. 9-0,8-1,7-2,6-3.","response_history":["6,","6. 9-0,8-1,7-2,6-3."],"rt":35277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":590486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, you cannot get 1,,3,5,7,9 from it.","response_history":["no, you cannot get 1,2,3","no, you cannot get 1,2,","no, you cannot get 1,2","no, you cannot get 1,,3,5,","no, you cannot get 1,,3,5.","no, you cannot get 1,,3,5,7,9 from it."],"rt":36016,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":626502,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, you can get all the numbers at some point.","response_history":["no","n","yes, you can get all the numbers at some point."],"rt":46915,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":673417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes ther are produced alond the way same as +6.","response_history":["yes, 10,","yes, 10-9=1, 1","yes, 10-9=1, ","yes, 10-","yes, 10","yes, 1","yes, ","yes,","yes ther are produced alond the way same as +6."],"rt":55517,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":728935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, it is a factor of 9.","response_history":["yes, it is a factor of 9."],"rt":12326,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":741261,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":6461,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":747722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"+n-1","response_history":["+n - 1","+n - ","+n -","+n ","+n-1, then t","+n-1, then ","+n-1, then==","+n-1, then=","+n-1, then","+n-1, the","+n-1, th","+n-1, t","+n-1, ","+n-1,","+n-1","+n-1"],"rt":43278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":791001,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"+n-x.","response_history":["+n-n","+n-x."],"rt":34643,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":825645,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I dont know, my mind is mushing.","response_history":["I dont know, my mid","I dont know, my mind is mushing."],"rt":30271,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":855916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["True","False"],"rt":12173,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":868090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4940,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":873030,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":145681,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1018712,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"false. because divisor would leave a remainder possibly?","response_history":["false. because divisor would leave a remainder possibly?"],"rt":87019,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1105733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an ele ment x i s a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":11448,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1117183,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"yes, or no. im not sure.","response_history":["maybe","yes, or no. im not sure."],"rt":46654,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1163838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a gen erator u nder +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":5143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1168981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1715,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1170697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"34","response_history":["34"],"rt":2272,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1172969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High sch ool dipl oma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":7513,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1180483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra 2","response_history":["Algebra 2"],"rt":8561,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1189045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3  - seen i t used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4552,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1193598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":8937,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1202535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something  from thi s HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4825,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1207361,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5735,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1213097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2331,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1215429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1837,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1217267,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":7137,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1224405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3663,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1228069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"ouch. I am going to go take a nap now.","response_history":["ouch. I am going to go take a nap now."],"rt":15763,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1243833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]